ADI ČAUŠEVIĆ

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Hauptstrasse 48, 8750 Glarus +41 76 824 9330 adi.causevic@protonmail.com



Age 24

Work permit Permit B

Software engineer with 6 years of programming experience, 1.5 of those in a proffesional environment. Used to working in agile environments where the main goal is to simplify seemingly complicated concepts to a user-friendly abstract level. Working on a Ph.D. in my free time with a focus on the security of AI. Always looking for solutions that are extendable and for ways to facilitate future work.

SKILLS

Languages

native Croatian foreign English C2

German **C1** Italian **A2**

Programming languages

advanced C++, Python intermediate C#, Java

basic Rust, Julia, Haskell, Bash, Julia,

JavaScript, SQL

Frameworks and libraries

Torch, Eigen, boost, boost::Python, WPF, SFML, Cuda, OpenCV, TensorFlow, Qt, SkLearn, Pandas,

Numpy

Development tools

Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, PyCharm, Clion, IntelliJ, CMake, git

WORK EXPERIENCE

November 2021 - October 2022 @ JC Development AG

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Maintained products in an agile environment Developed several products from ground-up

Designed PoCs and computed workload estimations for potential clients

Defined project scopes and feasibilities of different features

Lead the development of a product in an international surrounding

Organized weekly team meetings to improve our efficiency

Coached several intern and extern programmers in using CAD APIs

December 2016 - July 2017 @ IN2 d.o.o.

STUDENT INTERN

Took part in the organization of a programming course for children Designed tasks and defined goals of the workshop

Lead the workshop for children with intermediate programming skills

EDUCATION

2022 - present

Ph.D. in Computer Science (Subject: Security of AI)

RADBOUD UNIVERSITY NIJMEGEN, under supervision of D.S. Stjepan Picek

2019 - 2021

Master's degree programme in Computer Science (GPA 4.5/5.0) UNIVERSITY OF ZAGREB, FACULTY OF ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING AND COMPUTING, CROATIA

Thesis: Image Colorization Methods

Exchange student at

AGH University of Science and Technology, Krakow

University of Ljubljana, Faculty of Computer and Information Science

2016 - 2019

Bachelor's degree programme in Computer Science $(GPA\ 3.6/5.0)$ UNIVERSITY OF ZAGREB, FACULTY OF ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING AND COMPUTING, CROATIA

Thesis: Image Reconstruction Using a Fixed Number of Polygons